(Sheldon:)to Q&A from the audience?
(Penny(voice):)Yeah, I have a question.
(Penny(voice):)Is there anybody who can get me
the hell out of here
(Penny(voice):)and back to Los Angeles
tonight?
(Glenn(voice):)I'm driving back to L.A. tonight.
(Bernadette:)Penny, that's Glenn.
Glenn, that's Penny.
(Howard:)No!
(Penny:)SHELDON
Red Leader to Red Five.
(Sheldon:)Red Leader
to Red Five.
(Sheldon(voice):)Anybody up for a little game?
(Sheldon(voice):)I spy with my little eye...
(Sheldon(voice):)a nonferrous metal.
(Sheldon:)Must be out of range.
(Amy:)Leonard, can I ask you
a question?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
(Amy:)Are you bothered by the fact
that your former girlfriend
(Amy:)left the symposium
with what is probably
(Amy:)the most beautiful man
I've ever seen in my life?
(Leonard:)No. Why do you ask?
(Amy:)Because we're going
120 miles per hour.
(Sheldon:)All right, if no one's going
to guess...
I was spying the aluminum rims
on the police car
(Sheldon:)we passed a few miles back.